<Bible name="Malayalam Bible Theme">
	<Book id='healing'>
		<Chapter id='1'>“For I will restore health to you, and your wounds I will heal, declares the Lord” – Jeremiah 30:17″</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='2'>Heal my soul, for I have sinned against you.” – Psalm 41:4″</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='3'>But I will restore you to health and heal your wounds,’ declares the Lord, ‘because you are called an outcast, Zion for whom no one cares.” – Jeremiah 30:17″</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='4'>A cheerful heart is good medicine, but a crushed spirit dries up the bones.” – Proverbs 17:22</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='5'>“Is anyone among you sick? Let them call the elders of the church to pray over them and anoint them with oil in the name of the Lord.” – James 5:14</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='6'>Freely you have received; freely give.” – Matthew 10:8″</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='7'>Then they cried to the Lord in their trouble, and he saved them from their distress. He sent out his word and healed them; he rescued them from the grave.” – Psalm 107:19-20</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='8'>“Heal me, O Lord, and I will be healed; save me and I will be saved, for you are the one I praise.” – Jeremiah 17:14</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='9'>“And Jesus went about all Galilee, teaching in their synagogues, and preaching the gospel of the kingdom, and healing all manner of sickness and all manner of disease among the people.” – Matthew 4:23</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='10'>“But he was pierced for our transgressions, he was crushed for our iniquities; the punishment that brought us peace was on him, and by his wounds we are healed.” – Isaiah 53:5</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='11'>And the prayer offered in faith will make the sick person well; the Lord will raise them up. If they have sinned, they will be forgiven.” – James 5:15</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='12'>“Heal me, Lord, and I will be healed; save me and I will be saved, for you are the one I praise.” – Jeremiah 33:6</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='13'>“I will restore you to health and heal your wounds,’ declares the Lord.” – Jeremiah 30:17</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='14'>“He himself bore our sins in his body on the cross, so that we might die to sins and live for righteousness; by his wounds you have been healed.” – 1 Peter 2:24</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='15'>“He heals the brokenhearted and binds up their wounds.” – Psalm 147:3</Chapter>
	</Book>
	<Book id = 'faith'>
		<Chapter id='1'>“Now faith is the assurance of things hoped for, the conviction of things not seen.” – Hebrews 11:1</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='2'>“And without faith it is impossible to please him, for whoever would draw near to God must believe that he exists and that he rewards those who seek him.” – Hebrews 11:6</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='3'>“For by grace you have been saved through faith. And this is not your own doing; it is the gift of God.” – Ephesians 2:8</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='4'>“Therefore, since we have been justified by faith, we have peace with God through our Lord Jesus Christ.” – Romans 5:1</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='5'>“And Jesus answered them, ‘Have faith in God.'” – Mark 11:22</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='6'>“And whatever you ask in prayer, you will receive, if you have faith.” – Matthew 21:22</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='7'>“But let him ask in faith, with no doubting, for the one who doubts is like a wave of the sea that is driven and tossed by the wind.” – James 1:6</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='8'>“For in Christ Jesus you are all sons of God, through faith.” – Galatians 3:26</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='9'>“I have been crucified with Christ. It is no longer I who live, but Christ who lives in me. And the life I now live in the flesh I live by faith in the Son of God, who loved me and gave himself for me.” – Galatians 2:20</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='10'>“So faith comes from hearing, and hearing through the word of Christ.” – Romans 10:17</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='11'>“But my righteous one shall live by faith, and if he shrinks back, my soul has no pleasure in him.” – Hebrews 10:38</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='12'>“And Jesus said to him, ‘Go your way; your faith has made you well.’ And immediately he recovered his sight and followed him on the way.” – Mark 10:52</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='13'>“For everyone who has been born of God overcomes the world. And this is the victory that has overcome the world—our faith.” – 1 John 5:4</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='14'>“And the Lord said, ‘If you had faith like a grain of mustard seed, you could say to this mulberry tree, “Be uprooted and planted in the sea,” and it would obey you.'” – Luke 17:6</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='15'>“And Jesus said to them, ‘I am the bread of life. Whoever comes to me shall not hunger, and whoever believes in me shall never thirst.'” – John 6:35</Chapter>
	</Book>
	<Book id = 'thanksgiving'>
		<Chapter id='1'>“Give thanks to the LORD, for he is good; his love endures forever.” – Psalm 107:1</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='2'>“Do not be anxious about anything, but in every situation, by prayer and petition, with thanksgiving, present your requests to God.” – Philippians 4:6</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='3'>“Let them give thanks to the LORD for his unfailing love and his wonderful deeds for mankind.” – Psalm 107:8</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='4'>“Give thanks in all circumstances; for this is God’s will for you in Christ Jesus.” – 1 Thessalonians 5:18</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='5'>“Sing to the LORD with grateful praise; make music to our God on the harp.” – Psalm 147:7</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='6'>“Let the peace of Christ rule in your hearts, since as members of one body you were called to peace. And be thankful.” – Colossians 3:15</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='7'>“I will give thanks to you, LORD, with all my heart; I will tell of all your wonderful deeds.” – Psalm 9:1</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='8'>“Let us come before him with thanksgiving and extol him with music and song.” – Psalm 95:2</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='9'>“Enter his gates with thanksgiving and his courts with praise; give thanks to him and praise his name.” – Psalm 100:4</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='10'>“And whatever you do, whether in word or deed, do it all in the name of the Lord Jesus, giving thanks to God the Father through him.” – Colossians 3:17</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='11'>“Oh, give thanks to the LORD, for he is good! For his mercy endures forever.” – Psalm 107:1</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='12'>"Give thanks to the Lord, for he is good; his love endures forever." -1 Chronicles 16:34 </Chapter>
		<Chapter id='13'>"Devote yourselves to prayer, being watchful and thankful."- Colossians 4:2 </Chapter>
		<Chapter id='14'>"But blessed are your eyes because they see, and your ears because they hear." - Matthew 13:16 </Chapter>
		<Chapter id='15'>"Rejoice always, pray continually, give thanks in all circumstances; for this is God’s will for you in Christ Jesus." - 1 Thessalonians 5:16-18</Chapter>
	</Book>
	<Book id = 'protection'>
		<Chapter id='1'>He will cover you with his feathers, and under his wings you will find refuge; his faithfulness will be your shield and rampart. Psalm 91:4</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='2'>“The name of the Lord is a strong tower; the righteous run to it and are safe.”-Proverbs 18:10 </Chapter>
		<Chapter id='3'>“Fear not, for I am with you; be not dismayed, for I am your God. I will strengthen you, Yes, I will help you, I will uphold you with My righteous right hand.”- Isaiah 41:10 </Chapter>
		<Chapter id='4'>“God is our refuge and strength, a very present help in trouble.”- Psalm 46:1 </Chapter>
		<Chapter id='5'>“The angel of the Lord encamps all around those who fear Him, and delivers them.”- Psalm 34:7 </Chapter>
		<Chapter id='6'>“The Lord shall preserve you from all evil; He shall preserve your soul. The Lord shall preserve your going out and your coming in from this time forth, and even forevermore.”- Psalm 121:7-8</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='7'>“But the Lord is faithful, who will establish you and guard you from the evil one.”- 2 Thessalonians 3:3 </Chapter>
		<Chapter id='8'>“The Lord will fight for you, and you shall hold your peace.”- Exodus 14:14</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='9'>“The Lord is my rock and my fortress and my deliverer; my God, my strength, in whom I will trust; my shield and the horn of my salvation, my stronghold.”- Psalm 18:2</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='10'>“The Lord is your keeper; the Lord is your shade at your right hand.”-Psalm 121:5</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='11'>“Trust in the Lord with all your heart, and lean not on your own understanding; In all your ways acknowledge Him, and He shall direct your paths.”- Proverbs 3:5-6</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='12'>“You are my hiding place; You shall preserve me from trouble; You shall surround me with songs of deliverance.”- Psalm 32:7</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='13'>“The Lord is my light and my salvation; whom shall I fear? The Lord is the strength of my life; of whom shall I be afraid?”- Psalm 27:1</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='14'>“I will say of the Lord, ‘He is my refuge and my fortress; my God, in Him I will trust.”- Psalm 91:2</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='15'>“As the mountains surround Jerusalem, so the Lord surrounds His people from this time forth and forever.”- Psalm 125:2</Chapter>
	</Book>
	<Book id = 'patience'>
		<Chapter id='1'>“But if we hope for what we do not see, we wait for it with patience.” – Romans 8:25</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='2'>“Whoever is slow to anger has great understanding, but he who has a hasty temper exalts folly.” – Proverbs 14:29</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='3'>“But let patience have its perfect work, that you may be perfect and complete, lacking nothing.” – James 1:4</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='4'>“Love is patient, love is kind. It does not envy, it does not boast, it is not proud.” – 1 Corinthians 13:4</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='5'>“Rejoice in hope, be patient in tribulation, be constant in prayer.” – Romans 12:12</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='6'>“Be still before the Lord and wait patiently for him; fret not yourself over the one who prospers in his way, over the man who carries out evil devices!” – Psalm 37:7</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='7'>“And we urge you, brothers, admonish the idle, encourage the fainthearted, help the weak, be patient with them all.” – 1 Thessalonians 5:14</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='8'>“The Lord is not slow to fulfill his promise as some count slowness, but is patient toward you, not wishing that any should perish, but that all should reach repentance.” – 2 Peter 3:9</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='9'>“Better is the end of a thing than its beginning, and the patient in spirit is better than the proud in spirit.” – Ecclesiastes 7:8</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='10'>“Wait for the Lord; be strong, and let your heart take courage; wait for the Lord!” – Psalm 27:14</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='11'>“For you have need of endurance, so that when you have done the will of God you may receive what is promised.” – Hebrews 10:36</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='12'>“A hot-tempered man stirs up strife, but he who is slow to anger quiets contention.” – Proverbs 15:18</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='13'>“Let us not become weary in doing good, for at the proper time we will reap a harvest if we do not give up.” – Galatians 6:9</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='14'>“The Lord is merciful and gracious, slow to anger and abounding in steadfast love.” – Psalm 103:8</Chapter>
		<Chapter id='15'>“For whatever was written in former days was written for our instruction, that through endurance and through the encouragement of the Scriptures we might have hope.” – Romans 15:4</Chapter>
	</Book>	
</Bible>
